A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General, Program, and Project Photographs, 3
  - International Training and Research (ITR), 3_8
    - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - International Studies Program, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1533)
    - University of Chicago - Graduate Student Training in Latin American Studies, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1534)
    - University of Southern California (USC) - International Studies Program, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1535)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Library Studies Program, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 1536)
    - University of Wisconsin - Latin America, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 1537)
    - Washington University, St. Louis - Latin American Studies Program, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1538)
  - National Affairs (NA), 3_9
    - American Film Institute, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1539)
    - American Institute for Research - Project PACE, San Francisco, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1540)
    - Architects Renewal Committee in Harlem (ARCH), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 1541)
    - Aspira, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1542)
    - Brooklyn Linear City, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 1969)
    - Cheetah Charter Bus Service Co. (PRI), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 1543)
    - Chicago Conference on Religion and Race, 1968-1969 (Box 91, Folder 1544)
    - Cleveland Foundation - AIM-JOBs and Mayor Stokes, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1545)
    - Community Progress, Inc., New Haven Connecticut, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1546)
    - Congaree Iron and Steel Co. Inc. (PRI), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1547)
    - Connecticut Housing Investment Fund, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 1548)
    - Council of Equal Business Opportunity - Ebony Supermarket, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 1549)
    - East-Central Catfish Operations, Inc. (PRI) - Catfish farming, Sparta GA (Box 91, Folder 1550)
    - Federal Executive Institute, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1551)
    - International Self-Help Housing Associates, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 1553)
    - HELP - Mexican American Weavers - Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1968-1973 (Box 91, Folder 1552, Box 136, Folder 1971)
    - MACE (Mississippi Action for Community Education), 1973 April (Box 91, Folder 1554)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund (MALDEF), 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1555)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society - Environmental Education, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1556)
    - Spindletop Research, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1557)
    - Migrant Workers / Mexican Americans (from Denver Post, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1558)
    - Minority Contractors, 1973 July (Box 91, Folder 1559)
    - National Industrial Conference Board of E=Negro Employment, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 1561)
    - Mississippi Research and Development Center, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1560, Box 136, Folder 1970)
    - National Urban League - Whitney Young Jr., Exec Director, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 1562)
    - "The Near Side of Federalism: improving State and Local Government" photographs, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 1563)
    - Negro Mayors: Stokes of Cleveland, Hatcher of Gary, and Washington of Washington DC (Box 91, Folder 1564)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services, Washington DC (Box 91, Folder 1565)
    - Police - New York City, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 1566)
    - Progress Plaza Shopping Center / Zion Baptist Enterprises (PRI), 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1567)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund (PRLDEF), 1976 (Box 91, Folder 1568)
    - Southern Consumers' Co-ops, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1569)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Development of Education for City Planning, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1570)
    - Upper Park Avenue Community Association (UPACA), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1571)
    - Urban Coalition - John Gardner, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1572)
    - West Virginia Bet Corporation (PRI), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1573)
    - White House Interns, with President Lyndon B. Johnson, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 1972)
  - Overseas Development (OD), 3_10
    - Agriculture (general photographs), 1960s-1970s (Box 92, Folder 1574)
      Misc. general photographs.
    - Ford Foundation Overseas Development Officers' Luncheon Meeting, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 1575)
    - "Language Doors: foreign Language Training and the Teaching of English as a Second Language" booklet photographs, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 1576)
    - Seminar on the Development and Organization of Vocational Training and Technical Education, Denmark, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1577)
    - Africa (general photographs), 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1578)
    - Africa - African Courts, 1960s (Box 92, Folder 1579)
    - Argentina - Bariloche Foundation, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1580)
    - Argentina - Ford Foundation Field Office, Buenos Aires, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1581)
    - Argentina - National Council of Scientific and Technical Research, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 1582)
    - Argentina - Torcuato di Tella Institute, 1963 (Box 92, Folder 1583)
    - Argentina - University of Buenos Aires, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1584)
    - Argentina - Vocational Education, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 1585)
    - Brazil (general photographs), 1960s (Box 92, Folder 1586)
    - Brazil - American International Association for Economic and Social Development, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1587)
    - Brazil - Brazilian Center for Research in Physics, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1588)
    - Brazil - Brazilian Institute for Education Science and Culture - training of Secondary Science Teachers, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1589)
    - Brazil - State of Guanabara - Primary Education in Slum Area Outside Rio de Janeiro, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1590)
    - British East Africa - Makerere College - Housing for visiting scholars (Box 92, Folder 1591)
    - Burma - Agricultural Extension, Agriculture Institute at Pyinmana, 1954-1955 (Box 92, Folder 1592)
    - Burma - Faculty of Agriculture of University at Mandalay, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1593)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06000464 (PA60-464), Government of the Union of Burma.
    - Burma - Translation Society, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 1594)
    - Burma - University of Mandalay - Science Teaching Project, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1595)
    - Burma - University of Rangoon - Teaching and Research in Statistics and Agricultural Economics, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1596)
    - Burma Rangoon Technical High School, 1959 (Box 136, Folder 1974)
    - Burma University of Rangoon, 1959 (Box 136, Folder 1974)
    - Burma International Institute of Buddhistic Studies, 1959 (Box 136, Folder 1974)
    - Burma State Agricultural Institute, 1959 (Box 136, Folder 1974)
    - Chile (general photographs) (Box 93, Folder 1597)
    - Chile - Catholic University of Chile (Santiago), 1965 (Box 93, Folder 1598)
    - Chile - Community Development, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 1599)
    - Chile - Pontifical Catholic University of Chile, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 1600)
    - Chile - Regional Planning Division, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 1601)
    - Chile - University of Concepcion, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 1602)
    - Chile - University of Concepcion - Central Science Institute, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 1603)
    - Colombia - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT) (Box 93, Folder 1604)
    - Colombia - Industrial University of Santander - University of the Valley (Box 93, Folder 1605)
    - Colombia - University of the Andes, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1606)
    - Congo - Lovanium University, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1607)
    - Congo - National School of Law and Administration in the Congo (EDNA), Leopoldville, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1608)
    - Egypt - American University at Cairo, Nubian Resettlement Survey, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1609)
    - Ethiopia - Haile Selassie I university Law School (Box 93, Folder 1610)
    - Ecuador (general photographs), 1980 (Box 93, Folder 1611)
    - Ghana (general photographs), 1963 (Box 93, Folder 1612)
    - Ghana - Congress of Africanists, Accra, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1613)
    - Greece - Athens Technological Organization, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1614)
    - India (general photographs), 1950s-1960s (Box 93, Folder 1615)
    - India - General photographs from CBS, 'Population Explosion', 1960 (Box 93, Folder 1616)
    - India - Calcutta (general photographs), 1965-1966 (Box 93, Folder 1617)
      Misc. general street photographs, T.S. Saytan
    - India - Calcutta Metropolitan Planning Organization - press release, 1961 July 30 (Box 93, Folder 1618)
    - India - Calcutta - Urban Planning, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1619)
    - India - College of Agricultural Sciences, Bangalore - Plant Protection Research and Extension, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1620)
    - India - College of Home Science, Baroda, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 1621)
    - India - Delhi university - Language Laboratory, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1622)
    - India - Ford Foundation program chart, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 1623)
    - India - Punjab Agricultural University, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1624)
    - India - Tanjore Rice Paddy Conversion Program, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1625)
    - India - Wheat Harvest in Ludhiana, Punjab, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1626)
    - Indonesia - Clerical Skills Training Program, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 1627)
    - Indonesia - English Language Class, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 1628)
    - Indonesia - English language Teacher Training Program, 1957 (Box 94, Folder 1629)
    - Indonesia - FKIP's University of Malang Training of Secondary Science Teachers (Box 94, Folder 1630)
    - Iran - Gorgan Rural Development, Assistance for a Village Development Program, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1631)
    - Iran - Near East Foundation Demonstration Project, Mamazon, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 1632)
    - Israel - Israel Foundation Trustees, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1633)
    - Jamaica - College of the West Indies, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 1634)
    - Jordan - Cooperative Institute, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 1635)
    - Jordan - Junior College Program, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 1636)
    - Kenya - Educational Services Inc., 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1637)
    - Kenya - human Relations Workshop, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1638)
    - Kenya - Science Teaching in Secondary Schools, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1639)
    - Kenya - Seventh Inter-Africa Public Administration Seminar, Nairobi, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1640)
    - Kenya - Special Centre for English Language Instruction, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1641)
    - Kenya - Starehe Youth Centre, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1642)
    - Kenya - Strathmore College, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 1643)
    - Lebanon (general photographs), 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1644)
    - Lebanon - Beirut College for Women, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1645)
    - Lebanon - Ford Foundation Field Office, Beirut, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1646)
    - Lebanon - Ford Foundation Field Office, Beirut (negatives), 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1647)
    - Federation of Malaya (general photographs), 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1648)
    - Federation of Malaya - University of Malaya, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 1649)
    - Malaysia (general photographs), 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1650)
    - Malaysia - Family Planning, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1651)
    - Mexico (general photographs), 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1652)
      Photographs of various grantees.
    - Mexico - Autonomous University of Guadalajara - Mater Plan for Academic and Administrative Improvement, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1653)
    - Mexico - Autonomous University of Guadalajara Conference - National Polytechnic Institute, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1654)
    - Mexico - College of Mexico - Establishment of Center for Economic and Demographic Studies, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1655)
    - Mexico - Monterrey Institute of Technology and Advanced Studies, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1656)
    - Mexico - National Autonomous University of Mexico - Humanities and Philosophy, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1657)
    - Mexico - National Polytechnic Institute - Development of Scientific and Engineering Graduate Training (Box 94, Folder 1658)
    - Mexico - National School of Agriculture, Chapingo, 1963-1964 (Box 94, Folder 1659)
    - Mexico - National School of Agriculture - Development of Library and Establishment of a Statistical and Computing Center, Chapingo (Box 94, Folder 1660)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06300485 (PA63-485), National School Of Agriculture.
    - Nepal - Katmandu Cottage Industries (Box 95, Folder 1661)
    - Nicaragua - Univesity of Nicaragua Faculty and Facilities for General Studies Program, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 1662)
    - Nigeria (general photographs), 1965-1968 (Box 95, Folder 1663)
    - Nigeria - Banking Seminar, Lagos, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 1664, Box 136, Folder 1975)
    - Nigeria - Educational Services Inc., 1965 (Box 95, Folder 1665)
    - Nigeria - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1666)
    - Nigeria - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA) - Dedication, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1667)
    - Nigeria - Kaduna Center, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 1668)
    - Nigeria - Secondary School Science Teaching, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1669)
    - Nigeria - Study of Art and Music, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1670)
    - Nigeria - University College, Ibadan, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 1671)
    - Nigeria - Villages and Government, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1672)
    - Pakistan (general photographs), 1962-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1673)
    - Pakistan - Adminstrative Staff College, Lahore, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1674)
    - Pakistan - Est Pakistan Population Control, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1675)
    - Pakistan - East Pakistan Family Planning, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1676)
    - Pakistan - East Pakistan - Pilot Program of Cooperative Agricultural Development - Comilla Academy for Village Development, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 1677, Box 139, Folder 1982)
    - Pakistan - Karachi Polytechnic Institue, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1678)
    - Pakistan - Town and urban Development, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 1679)
    - Peru (general photographs), 1970s (Box 95, Folder 1680)
    - Peru - Centro Internacional de la Papa (CIPAPA), 1979 (Box 95, Folder 1681)
    - Peru - Machipicchu (United Nations photographs), 1967 (Box 95, Folder 1682)
    - Philippines (general photographs), 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1683)
    - Philippines - Graduate Education in Business Administration, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1684)
    - Phillipines - International Rice research Institute (IRRI), Los Banos, 1964-1977 (Box 95, Folder 1685)
    - Philippines - University of the Philippines, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1686)
    - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico (Box 95, Folder 1687)
    - Saudi Arabia - Agricultural photogrpahs from Arabian American Oil Co. (ARAMCO) World Magazine, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 1688)
    - Senegal - University of Dakar, Institute of Pedagological Studies (Box 95, Folder 1689)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06200223 (PA62-223), University Of Dakar.
    - South Africa (general photographs), 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1690)
    - Sudan - Univesity of Khartoum (Box 95, Folder 1691)
    - Swaziland - Waterford School, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1692)
    - Syria - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA) (Box 95, Folder 1693)
    - Tanganyika - Civil Servants' Traiing Center (Box 96, Folder 1694)
    - Tanganyika - Dar-Es-Salaam Techical Institute, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 1695)
    - Tanzania (general photographs), 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1696)
      Misc. general phootgrpahs.
    - Tanzania - serengeti Research Institute, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 1697)
    - Thailand - Siam Society - Development of a Research Center, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 1698)
    - Tunisia - Pan Maghrebian Seminar on Public Administration, Henry Ford II's visit to Tunisia (Box 96, Folder 1699)
    - Tunisia - Secretarilal and Accounting School, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 1700)
    - Turkey (general photographs), 1962-1968 (Box 96, Folder 1701)
    - Turkey - Language Program - Middle East Techical University, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1702)
    - Turkey - Middle East Technical University (Box 96, Folder 1703)
    - Turkey - national Science Lycee, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1704)
    - Turkey - Primary Education, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 1705)
    - Uganda - University of East Africa - New Peak Method (Reading), 1960s (Box 96, Folder 1706)
    - United Arab Republic (general photographs), 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1707)
    - United Arab Republic - Anfoushy Fisheries Trainig Center, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1708)
    - United Arab Republic - Regional Planning of Aswan Governorate, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1709)
    - United Arab Republic (Syrian Region) -Rural Home Handicraft Industries (Box 96, Folder 1710)
    - Venezuela - Community Development and Municipal; Improvement, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 1711)
  - Population (POP), 3_11
    - Population and Family Planning (general photographs), 1960s-1970s (Box 96, Folder 1712)
    - Background and reference material re: Ford Foundation;s Population Progam, 1967-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1713, 1714)
    - Brazil - Family Planning - Sociedade de Bem-Estar Familiar no Brasil (BEMFAM), 1967-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1715)
    - Chinese Center for international Training in Family Planning, Taiwan, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 1716)
    - Denmark State Seruminstitut, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1717)
    - Emory University - Reproductive Biology - Charles E. Graham and John Preedy (Box 96, Folder 1718)
    - Emory University - Yerkes Regional Primate Research Center - Reproductive Biology (Box 96, Folder 1719)
    - India - Family Planning, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1720)
    - Johns Hopkins Univesity - Population, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1721)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Public Health School in Pakistan, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1722)
    - Karolinska Institute, Stockholm, Sweden, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1723)
    - Ted Spiegel photographs: Population and Birth Control, Mexico, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 1724)
    - National institute for Research in Dairying, England, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1725)
    - Population Council work in Taiwan, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1726)
    - Population Investigation Committee, London School of Economics, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 1727)
    - Salk Institute for Biological Studies, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 1728)
    - Sex Information and Education Council of the United States (SIECUS), 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1729)
    - Singapore Family Planning Association, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1730)
    - Strategies to Introduce Population Studies into a School System, Pilot Workshop, Baltimore, 1976 May 10-12 (Box 97, Folder 1731)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 07690299 (PA76-299), Planned Parenthood Association Of Maryland, Inc.
    - University of Cambridge - Research and Training in Reproductive Biology, 1966-1970 (Box 97, Folder 1732)
    - University of Chicago - Population Research Center - Philip Hauser, 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 1733)
    - University of Liverpool - Reproductive Biology, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1734)
    - University of Michigan - Population Research, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1735)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Population Studies Center, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 1736)
    - University of Notre Dame - Population Conference, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1737)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Primate Reproduction, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1738)
    - University of Pennsylvania - training and Research in Demography, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 1739)
    - Uruguay, Montevideo, Universidad de la Republica- Service of Obstetrical Physiology, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1740)
  - Problems of the Aging, 3_12
    - Health Services, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 1741)
    - Retirement /Older Workers (general photographs), 1960 (Box 97, Folder 1742)
  - Public Affairs (PA), 3_13
    - American Friends Service Committee - Youth for Service, San Francisco, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 1743)
    - American Political Science Association, Congressional Fellowships, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1744)
    - Brigham Yong University, Provo Experiment, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 1745)
    - "And Justice for All" (Box 97, Folder 1746)
    - Council of the Southern Mountains, Kentucky, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1747)
    - Council of the Southern Mountains, Kentucky - Research Studies, Education, on Urban and Regional Problems, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1748)
    - Howard University - Legal Education, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1749)
    - Joe Molnar - Editorial Photography (Box 97, Folder 1750)
    - Michigan State Institute - Land use Game, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 1751)
    - Mobilization for Youth, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1752)
    - Morgan State College, Maryland - Institute for Political Education, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1753)
    - Morgan State College, Maryland - Program of Education in Public Affairs, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1754)
    - National Association of Counties - General support, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1755)
    - North Carolina Fund, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 1756)
    - Opportunities for Youth Project, Seattle, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1757)
    - Phoenix Welfare Foundation Development of Careers for Youth Program, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1758)
    - Police Administration, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1759)
    - Poverty (general photographs), 1960s (Box 97, Folder 1760)
    - Research in Public Affairs - Governmental and Political Processes and Public Policies - Pomona College, Reed College, Swarthmore College, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 1761)
    - United Planning Organization, Washington DC, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1762)
    - University of California - Study of the Social, Economic, and Political Status of Mexican-Americans, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1763)
    - University of Louisville, Kentucky - Southern Police Institute Conference: Police Responsibility in Race Tension and Conflict, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 1764)
    - Urban Seminar for Clergy, Des Moines, Iowa, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 1765)
  - Public Broadcasting (PB), 3_14
    - "The Black Frontier", KUON-TV, University of Nebraska Television, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1766)
    - Broadcasters' Nonprofit Satellite System, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1767)
    - Children's Television Workshop, PBS (Box 98, Folder 1768)
    - "Communications and Society", Charles Siepmann, Channel 13, WNDT (Box 98, Folder 1769)
    - "The Electric Company", Children's Television Workshop, PBS, 1970s (Box 98, Folder 1770)
    - "Folk Guitar with Laura Weber", San Francisco, KQED, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 1771)
    - Fred Rogers, "Mister Rogers Neighborhood", 1970 (Box 98, Folder 1772)
    - Julia Child, "The French Chef", WGBH, Boston (Box 98, Folder 1773)
    - KCET, Channel 28, Los Angeles, "Cancion de la Raza", 1968-1969 (Box 98, Folder 1774)
    - KQED, San Francisco, CA (Box 98, Folder 1775)
      Includes publicity photographs of various KQED programs.
    - KUAT, University of Arizona, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1776)
      Includes Election coverage, Tucson Boys' Chorus, NET's "What's New", and "Southwest Chronicles".
    - National Educational Television (NET), 1960s-1970s (Box 98, Folder 1777)
      Includes publicity photographs of various NET programs.
    - News clippings and pres releases re: Ford Foundation grants in Public Broadcasting, 1968-1969 (Box 98, Folder 1778)
    - "The Newsman's Scope" booklet photographs, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1779)
    - "Night Call", Del Shields, United Methodist Church, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 1780)
    - Public Broadcating Service (PBS), 1960s-1970s (Box 99, Folder 1781)
      Misc. publicity photogrpahs of various PBS programs.
    - Public broadcasting and cable TV, 1970s (Box 99, Folder 1782)
      Misc. general photogrpahs.
    - Six30 (Box 99, Folder 1783, 1784)
    - "SOUL!", WNDT, Billy Taylor, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1785)
    - South Carolina Education Television Center, "Job Man Caravan", 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1786)
    - "Volume See", 1969 (Box 99, Folder 1787)
    - WJCT, Channel 7, Community Television Inc., Jacksonville, Florida - "Feedback", 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1788)
      Includes photographs and news clippings.
    - "Woman Alive!", PBS / WNET 13, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 1789)
    - WTTW Chicago - "Citites Game" program, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 1790)
    - WTTW Chicago - "Just Jazz", 1971 (Box 99, Folder 1791)
      Includes promotional publications.
    - WTTW Chicago - "Playing Games with the Future", and "War Games" programs, 1970s (Box 99, Folder 1792)
  - Resources and the Environment (R&E), 3_15
    - Resources and the Environment program, 1960s (Box 99, Folder 1793)